A Finding Aid to the Lucy R. Lippard Papers, 1930s-2007, bulk 1960s-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lipplucy
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1950s-2006; Series 2; 28.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-28, 51, OVs 54-63
  - Correspondence by Name, 1950s-2006; 2.1
    - Kossuth, Joseph, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Kossuth, Joseph, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Kossuth, Joseph, 1969-1979 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Kostelantz, Richard, 1969-1980 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Kozloff, Joyce, 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Kramer, Margia, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Kramer, Margia, 1981-1989 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Krasilovsky, Alexis Rafael, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 32)
      Oversized material housed in OV 56
    - Kunz, Alesia, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Kunzle, David, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Kusama, Yayoi, 1960s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 35-37)
      Includes photos of Kusama and a photo of her with Joseph Cornell
    - Kusama, Yayoi, circa 1966-1978 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - K, General: Ka, 1970s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - K, General: Ke-Ki, 1960s-2000 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - K, General: Kj-Ko, 1970s-1998 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - K, General: Kr-Ky, 1960s-1995 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - K, First Names Only, 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - K, Illegible, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - La Noue, Terence, circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Lacy, Suzanne, 1980s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Ladda, Justen, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Lamelas, David, circa 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Langer, Sandra (Cassandra) L., 1970s-1991 (Box 11, Folder 49-50)
    - Langmuir, Elizabeth Cross, 1960s-1991 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Lanyon, Ellen, 1970s-1992 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Lark, Sylvia, 1970s-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Lasch, Pat, 1975-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Latham, John, 1970s-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Leeson, Loraine, 1970s-1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Les Petites Bon-Bons, circa 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Levine, Jack, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Les, circa 1970-circa 1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - LeWitt, Sol, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Oversized material housed in OV 61
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Licht, Jenny, circa 1970s (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Light Impressions Gallery, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Lijn, Liliane, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Lindeman, Susan Nicky, circa 1980s (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Lippard, Margaret, 1960s-1984 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Lippard, Vernon W., 1970s-1984 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Lischka, Gerhard Johann, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Loeb, Judy, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Logemann, Jane, 1960s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Lois de la Haba Associates, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Long, Richard, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Long, Richard, 1969-1975 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Long, Richard, 1976-1989 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Louw, Roelof, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1971-1998 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Lowe, R. Edward, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Lunden, Duane, 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - L, General: L.-Lak, 1960s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - L, General: Lam-Lay, 1970s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - L, General: Le-Len, 1960s-2005 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - L, General: Leo-Ley, 1960s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - L, General: Li, 1970s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - L, General: Ll-Lo, 1970s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - L, General: Lu-Ly, 1960s-2000 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - L, First Names Only, 1960s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - L, Illegible, circa 1980s (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Majeski, Mark, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Malloy, Mike, circa 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Malloy, Mike, "Conference of the Society of Cemetery Aestheticians", 1971; 1 sound tape reels includes transcript in Box 12, Folder 46 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Maloney, Martin, circa 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mangold, Robert and Sylvia, 1960s-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Marioni, Tom and Fish, Allan (Museum of Conceptual Art), circa 1969-circa 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Markovitz, Sherry, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Mayers, Natasha, circa 1980s-1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Mazzello, Carolyn, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 3
    - McGinnis, Mark W., circa 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - McLean, Bruce, circa 1969-1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - McMaugh, Alison, 1970s-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Mendieta, Ana, circa 1978-1984 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Includes note from Carl Andre
    - Merz, Mario, circa 1960s-circa 1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, circa 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Metzger, Deena, 1970s-1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Miami University, 1975-1993 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Miller, Brenda, 1971, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Lee Anne, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Miller, Marc H. and Ringma, Bettie, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      includes "paparazzi self-portraits" of Miller and Ringma with Bella Abzu, Angela Davis, Michael Collins, Joseph Hirshhorn, Andy Warhol and others
    - Millet, Kate, 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Missoula Museum of the Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Mogul, Susan Roberta, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Mollett, Michael, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Montano, Linda, 1980s-1991 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Moore, Claire, 1971-1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Moore College of Art, 1970-1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Moore, Lindy Lyman, 1974-1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Moore, Sabra, circa 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Moore, Sasha, circa 1980s-1992 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Mother Jones, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Morgan, Maud, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Morgan, Robert, circa 1972-1984 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Morris, Robert, 1960s-1972 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Ms. Magazine, 1972-1983 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Mulick, Nancy, circa 1976-1987 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Muntadas, Antonio, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Murphy, Marilyn, circa 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Murray State University, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Musée National d'Art Moderne, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Museum of Modern Art, circa 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 39-40)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 41-43)
    - Museum of Modern Art, circa 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1974-1990 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - M, General: M.-Mann, 1970s-2000 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - M, General: Mano-Mar, 1960s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - M, General: Mas-Maz, 1970s-1998 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - M, General: McC-McF, 1960s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - M, General: McG-McT, 1970s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - M, General: Mea-Men, 1960s-1997 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - M, General: Mer-Mez, 1970s-1995 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - M, General: Mi, 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - M, General: Mob-Mon, 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - M, General: Moo-Mori, 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - M, General: Morr-Moz, 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - M, General: Mu-My, 1960s-1980s (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - M, First Names Only: M.-Ma, 1970s-1980s (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - M, First Names Only: Mc-Mu, 1960s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), circa 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 8-10)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), circa 1966-1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter), 1971-1974; 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Nabakowski, Gislind, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Nading, Lee, circa 1981-circa 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Naidus, Beverly, 1979-1992 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - National Council on the Arts/National Endowment for the Arts, 1970-1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Nauman, Bruce, circa 1966-1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Nelson, Donna, 1970s (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Nemec, Vernita, circa 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Neuhaus, Max, 1966-1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - New Dimensions, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - New Museum, 1970s-1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1970s (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - New York Cultural Center, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - New York Feminist Art Institute, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - New York University, 1970-1977 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Newmarch, Annie, 1970s-1980s (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Nicaraguan Cultural Alliance, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Ninart and Cuban-American Art, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Nixon, John, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Noah, Barbara, 1970s-1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Non-Phenomena Foundation, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - North Carolina Museum of Fine Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Notable American Women, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - N, General: N.-National A, 1970s-1997 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - N, General: National C-Naz, 1970s-1980s (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - N, General: Nef-Nev, 1970s-2000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - New Art-New York, 1960s-2006 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Newark-Newton, 1980s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - N, General: Ni-Ny, 1960s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 49)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51 Folder 3
    - N, First Names Only, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Oatman, Christine, 1970s-1980 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Ogust, Richard, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - O'Hara, Morgan, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Ohio State University, 1967-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1965-1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Onslow-Ford, Gordon, 1965-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Orders and Co., 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - O'Shea, Hannah, 1970s-1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Ostrow, Saul, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - O, General: Ob-Ol, 1960s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - O, General: Om-Or, 1970s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - O, General: Os-Ow, 1960s-2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - O, First Names Only, circa 1980s (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Pagonis, Illyas, 1960s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Parks, Ti, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Parr, Herb, circa 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Parsons, Bruce, 1971-1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Paternosta, Cesar, 1969-1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Pearson, Henry (Hank), circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Pearson, Henry (Hank), 1961-1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Pearson, Henry (Hank), 1975-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Pearson, John, circa 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Pechter, Paul, circa 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Perreault, John, circa 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Pezold, Frederike, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Phillips Academy, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Picard, Lil, circa 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Pindell, Howardena, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Pindell, Howardena, 1970-1984 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Pinto, Jody, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Piper, Adrian, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Pittore, Carlo, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Plural, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Poe, Joy, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Political Art Documentation/Distribution (PAD/D) Recordings, circa 1980s; 3 Sound cassettes cassette labels include: "Union Made," "Diaz and Monterosa," and "Alejria" side A and "Sosa" side B. (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Political Art Documentation/Distribution (PAD/D) Recordings, circa 1980s; 3 Sound cassettes cassette labels include: "Arturo Arias at Roland's with Artists Call May 4th 1984," presumably PADD journal "Artists Call Against US Intervention in Central America" "Missik Saenz/Gallo" side A and "Michele Nachlios" side B; "end of beginning Miguel Angel Parada Oct. 6 '83" side A and "Middle Miguel Angel Parada" side B. (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Political Art Documentation/Distribution (PAD/D) Recordings, circa 1980s; 2 Sound cassettes cassette labels include "Coe/Van Dalen, 2nd Sunday April '84" (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Political Art Documentation/Distribution (PAD/D) Recordings, circa 1980s; 3 Sound cassettes cassette labels include "Asian-Hispanic PADD" and "Artists Call" (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Polony, Csaba, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Portland Center for the Visual Arts, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Powerhouse Gallery, 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Price, Sally, circa 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Printed Matter, Inc., 1970s-1989 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Pulsa, circa 1967-circa 1975 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Pulsa, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Pulsa, 1970-1975 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Purdue University, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - P, General: P.-Pal, 1960s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - P, General: Pan-Pau, 1960s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - P, General: Pea-Pen, 1970s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - P, General: Per-Ph, 1960s-1990s (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - P, General: Pi-Pl, 1960s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - P, General, Po, 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - P, General: Pr-Pu, 1960s-2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - P, First Names Only, 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Queen's University at Kingston, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Q, General, 1960s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Q, First Names Only, circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Rabinovitch, Bill (Rabinovitch and Guerra Gallery), 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Rabkin, Dorothy and Leo, 1960s-1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Rahmani, Aviva, 1973-1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ramos, Tony D., 1970s-1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Randolph, Lynn, 1980s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Raven, Arlene, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Red Belt Club, circa 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Reder, Ronnie, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Reed College, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Reid, Terry, circa 1970s-1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      Oversized material housed in OV 57
    - Reif, Russell Eliot, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Reise, Barbara, 1960s-1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Revelle, Barbara Jo, 1980s-1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Rice, Shelley, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Richard Demarco Gallery Ltd., 1975-1989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Rickaby, Tony, 1970s (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Ringgold, Faith, 1970s-1983 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Rinke, Klaus, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 25)
      Includes photos of Rinke; oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 5
    - Roberts, Mimi, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Rockburne, Dorothea, 1970s (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Rohm, Robert, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Rolfe, Nigel and Angela, 1970s-1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Romero, Rachel and Klayman, Leo, 1970s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Root, Step. L., circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Rosenbach, Ulrike, circa 1970-1976 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Rosenbach, Ulrike, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Rosenberg, Avis Lang, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Rosenberg Era Art Project, 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Rosenblum, Illith (I. Rose), 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Rosenquist, James, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1964-1986 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Rosenquist, James, Photographs, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 39)
      Includes photos of Rosenquist
    - Rosenthal, Rachel, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Rosler, Martha, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 41)
      Includes photos of Rosler
    - Rosler, Martha, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Rosler, Martha, 1977-1988 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Ross, Laura, 1970s-1983 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Ross, Nan and Stu, 1960s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Roth, Moira, circa 1980-1992 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Rubinstein, Linda, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Rupp, Christy, 1970-1990 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Ruppersberg, Allen, 1960s-1970s (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Ruscha, Edward, 1960s-1970s (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Russo, Carol, 1960s-1970s (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Rutovsky, Paul, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Rutzky, Ivy Sky, circa 1970s-1980 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Ryman, Ethan and Family, circa 1960s-circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - R, General: R.-Ra, 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - R, General: Re, 1970s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - R, General: Rh-Ri, 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - R, General: Rob-Rom, 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - R, General: Ros, 1960s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - R, General: Rot-Roy, 1960s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - R, General: Ru-Ry, 1970s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - R, First Names Only: R.-Ri, 1970s-1990s (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - R, First Names Only: Ro-Ru, 1960s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - R, Illegible, 1980, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - St. James Press Ltd., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Saint Louis Art Museum, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Salas, Vincent J., Jr., 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco Art Institute, 1960s-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco Mime Troupe, 1980s (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco State University, 1974; 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Sandler, Irving, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Santa Monica Museum of Art (Trisha Ziff), 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Santorro, Suzanne, 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Sao Paulo Biennale, 1960s-1970s (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Oversized material housed in OV 59
    - Save the Children Foundation, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Schapiro, Miriam (Mimi), 1961-1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51 Folder 5
    - Schneeman, Carolee, circa 1967-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - School of the Art Institute of Chicago, circa 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Seaman, Terry, 1970s-1981 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Semmel, Joan, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Sentis, Mireia, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Serra, Richard, circa 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Shapiro, Anna, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Sharon, Miriam, circa 1976-1988 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Sharon, Miriam, circa 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      Includes photos of Sharon; oversized material housed in OV 59
    - Sharon, Miriam, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Includes photos of Sharon
    - Sharon, Miriam, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Sharon, Miriam, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Sharon, Miriam, 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Shaw, Joyce Cutler, circa 1971-1992 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      Includes photo of Shaw
    - Shaw, Karen, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Shelton, Laurie, circa 1970s (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Sherk, Bonnie, 1970s-1985 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Siegel, Arthur and Irene, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Siegel, Arthur and Irene, 1969-1977 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Siegel, Irene, 1978-1989 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Siegel, Julie, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Siegel, Julie, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Siegel, Julie, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Siegel, Julie, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Siegelaub, Seth, 1985-1995 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Sills, Leslie, 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Singer, Michael, circa 1973-1987 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Sjoo, Monica, 1977-circa 1987 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Skoglund, Sandy, circa 1974 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Barbara, circa 1970s (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Smith College Museum of Art, 1970-1990 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Smith, M. J., 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1973-1991 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Smock, Kristine, 1980s (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Snow, Michael, 1960s-1970s (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Snyder, Joan, 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Society for Contemporary Art, 1971-1977 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Society for Folk Arts Preservation, Inc. (Evelyn A. Stern), 1977-1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Society of North American Goldsmiths, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Sondheim, Alan, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Sonfist, Alan, circa 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Sonnier, Keith, circa 1968-1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Specter, Naomi, circa 1968-1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Spero, Nancy, circa 1970s-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Spodarek, Diane, circa 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Stamets, Billl, circa 1978-circa 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Stamets, Bill, 1978-1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Stark, Suzanne, 1960s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - State University College, Fredonia, New York, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Stein, Sally, circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Steir, Pat, 1970s-1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Stevens, May, circa 1971-1994 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Stokes, Charlotte, 1970-1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Stone, Suzi, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Streeter, Tal, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Strider, Marjorie, 1967-1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Stromsten, Amy, circa 1971-1981 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Stuart, Michelle, circa 1970s-1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Stubbs, Ann, 1970s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Student Mobilization Committee Benefits Fund, circa 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Studio International (Richard Cork), 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Sweeney, Alice, 1979-1983 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - S, General: S.-Sam, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - S, General: San-Sav, 1960s-2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - S, General: Sc, 1960s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - S, General: Se, 1960s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - S, General: Sh, 1960s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - S, General: Si, 1960s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - S, General: Sk-Sl, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - S, General: Sm, 1960s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - S, General: Sn, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - S, General: Sod-Sot, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - S, General: Sou-Sq, 1960s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - S, General: Sta, 1970s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - S, General: Ste, 1960s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - S, General: Sto-Stu, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - S, General: Su-Sz, 1960s-2000 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - S, First Names Only, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - S, Illegible and Unidentified, 1978; 1982 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Tacha, Athena, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Tate Gallery, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Tavenner, Patricia, 1970s-1980 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Tavins, Paula, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Temkin, Merle, 1970s-1980s (Box 18, Folder 47)